Let's now continue learning important JavaScript features.
And one topic that we haven't touched yet
is asynchronous JavaScript.
So, the goal of asynchronous JavaScript
is basically to deal with long-running tasks,
that basically run in the background.
And the most common use case of asynchronous JavaScript
is to fetch data from remote servers,
in so-called AJAX calls.
And so, that's what we will do in this section,
while learning everything there is to learn
about Promises, the fetch function, async await,
and error handling.
So this is yet another really exciting section,
and so let's get started.
(gentle music)